[
  {
    "question_number": 1,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قصاص",
      "سجن",
      "حكم",
      "قضاء"
    ],
    "answer": "قضاء",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 2,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "نوم",
      "استرخاء",
      "راحة",
      "تمدد"
    ],
    "answer": "نوم",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 3,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "الاجتهاد",
      "الشهادة",
      "البيانات",
      "المعلومات"
    ],
    "answer": "الاجتهاد",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 4,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "شاب",
      "طفل",
      "كهل",
      "بطولة"
    ],
    "answer": "بطولة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 5,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "ماء",
      "نار",
      "عسل",
      "زيت"
    ],
    "answer": "نار",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 6,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "رمح",
      "محراب",
      "قوس",
      "قبة"
    ],
    "answer": "رمح",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 7,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "ضفدع",
      "تمساح",
      "سمكة",
      "سلحفاة"
    ],
    "answer": "سمكة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 8,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "منزل",
      "سكن",
      "مسجد",
      "مكان"
    ],
    "answer": "مكان",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 9,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "محاضرة",
      "جامعة",
      "مكتبة",
      "مدرسة"
    ],
    "answer": "محاضرة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 10,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "بسمة",
      "كره",
      "حزن",
      "حب"
    ],
    "answer": "بسمة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 11,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "إسلام",
      "إحسان",
      "إيمان",
      "إكرام"
    ],
    "answer": "إكرام",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 12,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "موظف",
      "عامل",
      "رئيس",
      "مراجع"
    ],
    "answer": "رئيس",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 13,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "حماية",
      "عناية",
      "حراسة",
      "وقاية"
    ],
    "answer": "عناية",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 14,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "الرياض",
      "البصرة",
      "صنعاء",
      "المنامة"
    ],
    "answer": "البصرة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 15,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "تلفاز",
      "جوال",
      "كاميرا",
      "حاسوب"
    ],
    "answer": "كاميرا",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 16,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "كرة السلة",
      "كرة اليد",
      "كرة الطائرة",
      "كرة القدم"
    ],
    "answer": "كرة القدم",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 17,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "السعادة",
      "البهجة",
      "الرضى",
      "السرور"
    ],
    "answer": "الرضى",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 18,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "اليوم",
      "الأسبوع",
      "الشهر",
      "القرن"
    ],
    "answer": "القرن",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 19,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "سنة",
      "قرن",
      "دهر",
      "شهر"
    ],
    "answer": "دهر",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 20,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "ارشادات",
      "تعليمات",
      "توجيهات",
      "اشادات"
    ],
    "answer": "اشادات",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 21,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "الجناح",
      "الأنف",
      "المنقار",
      "العين"
    ],
    "answer": "الجناح",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 22,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "شماغ",
      "غترة",
      "عمامة",
      "لثام(لثمة)"
    ],
    "answer": "لثام(لثمة)",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 23,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "عهد",
      "وعد",
      "فقد",
      "عقد"
    ],
    "answer": "فقد",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 24,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "معين",
      "مربع",
      "مستطيل",
      "مثلث"
    ],
    "answer": "مثلث",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 25,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "مثلث",
      "مربع",
      "مستطيل",
      "دائرة"
    ],
    "answer": "دائرة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 26,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "صاروخ",
      "سفينة",
      "قطار",
      "سيارة"
    ],
    "answer": "صاروخ",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 27,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "خلل",
      "الموت",
      "المرض",
      "عطل"
    ],
    "answer": "الموت",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 28,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "مقعد",
      "مشرط",
      "نور",
      "سماعة"
    ],
    "answer": "نور",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 29,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "محرك",
      "دراجة",
      "عجلة",
      "نور"
    ],
    "answer": "نور",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 30,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "عجلة",
      "نور",
      "مقود",
      "محرك"
    ],
    "answer": "نور",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 31,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "غش",
      "ربح",
      "خسارة",
      "تجارة"
    ],
    "answer": "غش",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 32,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "هند",
      "منال",
      "ريم",
      "شهد"
    ],
    "answer": "منال",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 33,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "ملعب",
      "مضرب",
      "طيارة",
      "سيارة"
    ],
    "answer": "ملعب",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 34,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "دين",
      "نبي",
      "قياس"
    ],
    "answer": "دين",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 35,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "إجماع",
      "سنة",
      "نبي",
      "قياس"
    ],
    "answer": "نبي",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 36,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "فصل",
      "باب",
      "عرض",
      "مقدمة"
    ],
    "answer": "عرض",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 37,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "الماء",
      "الهواء",
      "الزجاج",
      "الحديد"
    ],
    "answer": "الهواء",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 38,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "مجرى",
      "وادي",
      "مسيل",
      "النهر"
    ],
    "answer": "وادي",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 39,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "خسوف",
      "كسوف",
      "برق",
      "براكين"
    ],
    "answer": "براكين",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 40,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "عقد",
      "فستان",
      "قميص",
      "خلخال"
    ],
    "answer": "قميص",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 41,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "وضوء",
      "تيمم",
      "اغتسال",
      "تنظيف"
    ],
    "answer": "تنظيف",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 42,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "حصن",
      "سياج",
      "سور",
      "جدار"
    ],
    "answer": "حصن",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 43,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "سراج",
      "جدار",
      "حصن",
      "سور"
    ],
    "answer": "سراج",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 44,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "تدارس",
      "تنقل",
      "تحدي",
      "توجيه"
    ],
    "answer": "تنقل",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 45,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "القمر",
      "الغذاء",
      "الشمس",
      "الماء"
    ],
    "answer": "القمر",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 46,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "هضاب",
      "تلال",
      "نجوم",
      "صخور"
    ],
    "answer": "نجوم",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 47,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "طالب",
      "معلم",
      "مدرب",
      "طبيب"
    ],
    "answer": "طالب",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 48,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "داوود",
      "خالد",
      "علي",
      "عمر"
    ],
    "answer": "داوود",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 49,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "زواج",
      "مصافحة",
      "طلاق",
      "مصارعة"
    ],
    "answer": "مصارعة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 50,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "نحيب",
      "نشيج",
      "عويل",
      "بكاء"
    ],
    "answer": "بكاء",
    "exam": "الاختبار الأول (المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 51,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "صداقة",
      "وفاء",
      "تضحية",
      "فداء"
    ],
    "answer": "صداقة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 52,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "نجوم",
      "شمس",
      "سراج",
      "شموع"
    ],
    "answer": "نجوم",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 53,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "غواص",
      "مرجان",
      "شُعب",
      "نجم البحر"
    ],
    "answer": "غواص",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 54,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "الأحد",
      "الاثنين",
      "الثلاثاء",
      "الخميس"
    ],
    "answer": "الخميس",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 55,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "يجري( يركض)",
      "يمشي",
      "يقفز",
      "يطير"
    ],
    "answer": "يطير",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 56,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قفز",
      "طيران",
      "ركض",
      "مشي"
    ],
    "answer": "طيران",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 57,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قراءة",
      "نسخ",
      "كتابة",
      "رسم"
    ],
    "answer": "قراءة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 58,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قرأ",
      "نسخ",
      "كتب",
      "رسم"
    ],
    "answer": "قرأ",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 59,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قميص",
      "ثوب",
      "سروال",
      "عمامة"
    ],
    "answer": "عمامة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 60,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "حليب",
      "بيض",
      "سكر",
      "عسل"
    ],
    "answer": "سكر",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 61,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "دعاء",
      "صوم",
      "زكاة",
      "طواف"
    ],
    "answer": "دعاء",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 62,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "عين",
      "أنف",
      "فم",
      "ذقن"
    ],
    "answer": "ذقن",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 63,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "أبوة",
      "عمومة",
      "خؤولة",
      "بنوة"
    ],
    "answer": "بنوة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 64,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "سيارة",
      "محرك",
      "مقود",
      "عجلات"
    ],
    "answer": "سيارة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 65,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "عن",
      "في",
      "على",
      "إلا"
    ],
    "answer": "إلا",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 66,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "دراجة",
      "قطار",
      "سيارة",
      "حافلة"
    ],
    "answer": "دراجة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 67,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قلم",
      "دفتر",
      "مسطرة",
      "حاسوب"
    ],
    "answer": "حاسوب",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 68,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "حاسب آلي",
      "قلم",
      "كتاب",
      "مسطرة"
    ],
    "answer": "حاسب آلي",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 69,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "فرس",
      "ناقة",
      "أتان",
      "زرافة"
    ],
    "answer": "زرافة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 70,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "لبؤة",
      "زرافة",
      "أتان",
      "فرس"
    ],
    "answer": "لبؤة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 71,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "لبؤة",
      "أسد",
      "زرافة",
      "مهرة"
    ],
    "answer": "أسد",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 72,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "ناقة",
      "لبؤة",
      "أتان",
      "فرس"
    ],
    "answer": "لبؤة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 73,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "حصان",
      "لبؤة",
      "زرافة",
      "أتان"
    ],
    "answer": "لبؤة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 74,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "أسد",
      "لبؤة",
      "فرس",
      "ناقة"
    ],
    "answer": "أسد",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 75,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "أستاذ مساعد",
      "أستاذ",
      "أستاذ مشارك",
      "معلم"
    ],
    "answer": "معلم",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 76,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "تسويف",
      "تشبيه",
      "تقريب",
      "تمثيل"
    ],
    "answer": "تسويف",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 77,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "التشبيه",
      "التخويف",
      "التمثيل",
      "التقريب"
    ],
    "answer": "التخويف",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 78,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "باهظ",
      "ثمين",
      "كثير",
      "غالي"
    ],
    "answer": "كثير",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 79,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "بر",
      "دقيق",
      "طحين",
      "عجين"
    ],
    "answer": "عجين",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 80,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "مكتبة",
      "مجلة",
      "كتاب",
      "بحث"
    ],
    "answer": "مكتبة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 81,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "مجلة",
      "جريدة",
      "وسيلة",
      "صحيفة"
    ],
    "answer": "وسيلة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 82,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "هدية",
      "نفقة",
      "هبة",
      "عطية"
    ],
    "answer": "نفقة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 83,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "ليل",
      "عصر",
      "فجر",
      "ظهر"
    ],
    "answer": "ليل",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 84,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "شجاع",
      "المحسن",
      "الكريم",
      "الجود"
    ],
    "answer": "الجود",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 85,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "المحسن",
      "المسيء",
      "المسامح",
      "المعاتب"
    ],
    "answer": "المسيء",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 86,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "لسن",
      "مهذار",
      "بليغ",
      "فصيح"
    ],
    "answer": "مهذار",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 87,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قصة",
      "رواية",
      "أدب",
      "أقصوصة"
    ],
    "answer": "أدب",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 88,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "صُم",
      "قـُم",
      "نَم",
      "تَم"
    ],
    "answer": "تَم",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 89,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "سقف",
      "باب",
      "جدار",
      "شجرة"
    ],
    "answer": "شجرة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 90,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "تجارة",
      "نماء",
      "بذخ",
      "زيادة"
    ],
    "answer": "بذخ",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 91,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "فوران",
      "غليان",
      "فيضان",
      "انصهار"
    ],
    "answer": "انصهار",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 92,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "فوران",
      "غليان",
      "فيضان",
      "ذوبان"
    ],
    "answer": "ذوبان",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 93,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "سفر",
      "فندق",
      "راحة",
      "سياحة"
    ],
    "answer": "سياحة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 94,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "حج",
      "سعي",
      "طواف",
      "رمي"
    ],
    "answer": "حج",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 95,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "نجم",
      "ليل",
      "شرق",
      "غرب"
    ],
    "answer": "ليل",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 96,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "نظارة",
      "ساعة",
      "حذاء",
      "رداء"
    ],
    "answer": "ساعة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 97,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "غرفة",
      "شقة",
      "بيت",
      "عمارة"
    ],
    "answer": "غرفة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 98,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "الرئتين",
      "القلب",
      "العين",
      "الكبد"
    ],
    "answer": "العين",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 99,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "حشد",
      "جماعة",
      "سرب",
      "قادات"
    ],
    "answer": "قادات",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 100,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "منهاج (نهج)",
      "طريق",
      "درب (سبيل )",
      "وضوح"
    ],
    "answer": "وضوح",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  }
]